# **BRIAN ROBERT CAJULIS**

## https://briancajulis.github.io/portfolio-website-v2/ • in https://www.linkedin.com/in/brian-robert-cajulis

### **SUMMARY**

Restorative Front End Developer with 2+ years of experience developing comprehensive code for web and mobile applications. Independently planned, designed, and developed features for both web and mobile applications at a fast paced startup company. Created a detailed workflow document which unified the development team and increased development rate. An adaptable team player and an analytical thinker.

#### **SKILLS**

Frameworks & Libraries: React, React Native, Redux, Axios

Programming Languages: JavaScript(ES6+), HTML, CSS, SASS, Java

#### **EXPERIENCES**

## **ENDORSIFY - SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

07/2018 to 10/2018 • Los Angeles, CA

- Completed full stack development tasks and solve challenging interface breaking bugs
- Created a secure REST API for the company's mobile application
- Collaborated with UX designer and transformed mock-ups into front end code
- Switched between web and mobile development tasks
- Reviewed code co-worker's code and provided detailed feedback to improve the code

## AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY - COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB TECHNICIAN

09/2017 to 05/2018 • Azusa, CA

AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY

- Guided students with object oriented programming and general algorithm concepts
- Assisted students in Java related issues
- Communicated with students in debugging various different web and mobile projects

# AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY - CS ACTION TEAM MEMBER

05/2016 to 06/2016 • Namibia, South Africa

- Interviewed target market to create user cases to specify software features
- Participated in meetings to plan and to discuss the implementation of each feature
- Quickly learned new frameworks and programming languages that were desired

### **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE

MAY 2018 AZUSA, CA

#### **PROJECTS**

## **COFFEE POT • SENIOR CAPSTONE PROJECT • 2017 TO 2018**

React Native, Redux, JavaScript, Firebase, Google APIs

- Coffee Pot is a mobile application used to deliver and order coffee using a peer-to-peer system
- Implemented Google Places API to fetch café places within a set mile radius and sort them according to distance

## MY CLUB • PERSONAL • 2018 TO CURRENT

React Native, Redux, JavaScript, Firebase

 My Club is a mobile application that would give club leaders a way to consistently engage with their club members and would give students more opportunities to join clubs easily